(
"ai_sub_version": "2.5.0",
"lyrics_prompt_version": 2,
"subtitles_prompt_version": 12,
"complete": true,
"max_retries_exceeded": false,
"settings": (
"ai": (
"model": null,
"model_subtitles": "gemini-cli:gemini-3-flash-preview",
"model_lyrics": "google-gla:gemini-3.1-flash-lite-preview",
"rpm": 4,
"tpm": 250000,
"web_search_tool": "duckduckgo",
"google": (
"file_cache_ttl": 10,
"use_files_api": true
),
"gemini_cli": (
"timeout": 600,
"overwrite_system_prompt": false
)
),
"split": (
"max_seconds": 300,
"re_encode": (
"enabled": true,
"fps": 1,
"height": 360,
"bitrate_kb": 35,
"threshold_mb": 20,
"duration_tolerance_ms": 100,
"encoder": "libx264"
),
"start_offset_min": 0
"thread": (
"uploads": 4,
"re_encode": 2,
"lyrics": 4,
"subtitles": 4
),
"retry": (
"run": 3,
"max": 9,
"delay": 30
),
"log": (
"level": "info",
"timestamps": true,
"scrub": false
)
フブキ！
Fubuki!
ミオ！
Mio!
おかゆ！
Okayu!
ころね！
Korone!
Ready? Go!
フブキ！
Fubuki!
Okay!
ミオ！
Mio!
おかゆ！
Okayu!
ころね！
Korone!
I'm ready!
フブキ！
Fubuki!
Perfect!
フブキ！
Fubuki!
ミオ！
Mio!
おかゆ！
Okayu!
Perfect!
天気がいい
The weather was nice
病気になりそうなほど眩しい日差しの中
In the dazzling sunlight that seemed to make you sick
することもないから君と駄弁っていた
Having nothing to do, I was chattering with you
「でもまぁ夏は嫌いかな」猫を撫でながら
"But well, I guess I hate summer," while stroking a cat
君は不貞腐れたような顔でそんなことを言った
You said such a thing with a sulky face
せーの！
One, two!
G I R I G I R I
もっともっと激しく
More and more intensely,
ギリギリを攻めて
pushing it to the edge.
ふたりなら行けるさ
If it's the two of us, we can go...
ギリギリを越えて
beyond the limit.
突き抜けよう Tonight
Let's break through tonight!
ギリギリを愛して
Loving the edge,
永遠を誓うよ
I'll vow eternity...
ギリギリの世界で
in this borderline world.
イェーイ！
Yeah!
G-A-M-E-R-S
フッフー！
Whoo-hoo!
G-A-M-E-R-S
いくよ！
Here we go!
あちょー！
A-cho!
ゆび！ゆび！ゆびゆび！
Fingers! Fingers! Yubi-yubi!
どぅーどぅーどぅーどぅーどぅー
Doo doo doo doo doo
ゆび！ゆび！ゆびゆび！
Fingers! Fingers! Yubi-yubi!
どぅーどぅーどぅーどぅーどぅー
Doo doo doo doo doo
待たせたなー！
I've kept you waiting!
戌神ころね！いきまーす！
Inugami Korone! Here I go!
わおーん！
Waooon!
次はフブキングだよー！
Next is Fubaking!
はーい！
Haaai!
いくよー！
Here I go!
Hi, Friends!
盛り上がってるー！？
Are you pumped up!?
最後まで楽しんでいってねー！
Please enjoy until the very end!
コンコンきーつね！
Kon kon kitsune!
白上フブキだよ！
I'm Shirakami Fubuki!
みんなー！大好きだよー！
Everyone! I love you all!
お待たせ！
Sorry for the wait!
猫又おかゆだよー！
I'm Nekomata Okayu!
一緒に楽しもうねー
Let's have fun together!
もぐもぐー？
Mogu mogu-?
おかゆー！
Okayu-!
ありがとー！
Thank you!
ラストはうちだよー！
And last is me!
大神ミオです！
I'm Ookami Mio!
全力でいくよー！
I'm going all out!
ミオしゃー！？
Miosha-!?
かわいいー！
So cute!
ありがとー！
Thank you!
以上！ホロライブゲーマーズでしたー！
That's all! We were Hololive Gamers!
バイバイー！
Bye-bye!
G-A-M-E-R-S
OK!
ころね！
Korone!
Are you ready?
おかゆ！
Okayu!
フブキ！
Fubuki!
みお！
Mio!
G-A-M-E-R-S
OK!
超ゲマズ
Super Gamers
ころね！
Korone!
むにゅ！
Munyu!
(G-A-M-E-R-S) We are GAMERS
Are you ready? Now!
Perfect!
(G-A-M-E-R-S) We are GAMERS
Hey! Hey! Hey! Hey!
むにゅ！
Munyu!
(G-A-M-E-R-S) We are GAMERS
(G-A-M-E-R-S)
Okay!
ころね！
Korone!
10!
9!
8!
7!
6!
5!
4!
3!
2!
1!
0!
ホロライブゲーマーズ！
hololive GAMERS!
WE ARE GAMERS!
いくぞー！
Here we go!
こんこんきつねが通ります
Kon-kon kitsune coming through!
白上フブキです 白上フブキです
It's Shirakami Fubuki, Shirakami Fubuki!
史上最強のスーパーアイドル
The strongest super idol in history!
君もスタッフに入門しなさい
You should join our staff too!
はい、せい！ イェイ！
One, say! Yay!
コンコンコンでコンコンコン
Kon-kon-kon, Kon-kon-kon!
ちょうだいな お祝いは おもち
Give me some mochi as a treat!
赤色よりも 金色がいいぞ わっしょい！
Gold is better than red! Wasshoi!
うちだよー！大神ミオだよー！
It's me! I'm Ookami Mio!
黒髪 ケモ耳 大神ミオ
Black hair, animal ears, Ookami Mio!
占ってみせます ライターママ
I'll give you a reading, I'm your Mama!
笑い出すと 止まらない ゲラゲラ
Once I start laughing, I can't stop! Gela-gela!
つまり うちは ポンコツ？
So, am I actually a klutz?
怖がらせちゃうかも？
I might end up scaring you!
タロット占いで 見る未来
Seeing the future with Tarot readings
ホラーゲーム やりたくない！
I don't want to play horror games!
四人揃えば ゲーマーズ最高
With the four of us, GAMERS are the best!
フラグが立てば 即回収
If a flag is raised, we'll clear it instantly
技を鍛えて 狙い撃ち
Hone our skills and take the shot
今日は 何プレイしよう？
What should we play today?
君のハートを 攻略しちゃうぜ
We're gonna conquer your heart!
選択をして シミュレーション
Make your choice and simulate
初見も コンプも 大歓迎
Blind runs or completions, all are welcome!
やっぱ ゲームは 楽しいね
As expected, games are so much fun!
WE ARE GAMERS!
もぐもぐおかゆ おにぎりおかゆ
Mogu mogu Okayu, Onigiri Okayu!
おにぎり おにぎり 白米最高
Onigiri, onigiri, rice is the best!
ヒラヒラフラフラ そこの猫だもん
Fluttering and drifting, I'm just a cat there
ホントは 構って 欲しいんじゃない？
Don't you actually want some attention?
まったり ゆったり 奏でるリズム
A relaxed and chill rhythm we play
全肯定する 深い愛
Deep love that affirms everything
全肯定 肯定 肯定 OK
Affirmation, affirmation, affirmation, OK!
毎日 僕と いいっしょ？
Isn't it great to be with me every day?
ゆびゆび〜 わんわん
Yubi yubi~ Wan wan!
戌神ころねだよ！
I'm Inugami Korone!
今日も レトロゲー 三昧
Today is full of retro games again
おやつは コロネ コロネ 戌神ころね
Snack time is Corone, Corone, Inugami Korone!
拳で 語るよ 熱い パッション
Speaking with my fists, a hot passion!
まずは 指を 捧げてくれる？
First, would you offer me your fingers?
わかったな 本気 出ちゃうぜ OK
Got it? I'm getting serious now, OK!
動物の如く ゲームをお届け
Delivering games like a wild animal!
四人揃えば ゲーマーズ最高
With the four of us, GAMERS are the best!
フラグが立てば 即回収
If a flag is raised, we'll clear it instantly
技を鍛えて 狙い撃ち
Hone our skills and take the shot
今日は 何プレイしよう？
What should we play today?
君のハートを 攻略しちゃうぜ
We're gonna conquer your heart!
選択をして シミュレーション
Make your choice and simulate
初見も コンプも 大歓迎
Blind runs or completions, all are welcome!
やっぱ ゲームは 楽しいね
As expected, games are so much fun!
突然ですが ボーナスチャレンジの時間よ！
All of a sudden, it's time for the bonus challenge!
大きな声で レスポンスして 得点稼いじゃいましょう！
Give us a loud response and earn some points!
ARE YOU READY?
SAY, KON KON!
KON KON!
MIO MIO!
MOGU MOGU!
YUBI YUBI!
KON KON! KON KON!
MIO MIO! MIO MIO!
MOGU MOGU! MOGU MOGU!
YUBI YUBI! YUBI YUBI!
PERFECT! YEAH!
四人揃えば ゲーマーズ最高
With the four of us, GAMERS are the best!
リモコンなくても 光合成
Photosynthesizing even without a remote
全クリするまで 諦めない
Won't give up until the game is cleared
エンディングを 見に行こう
Let's go see the ending!
君のハートを 攻略しちゃうぜ
We're gonna conquer your heart!
選択をして シミュレーション
Make your choice and simulate
初見も コンプも 大歓迎
Blind runs or completions, all are welcome!
やっぱ ゲームは 楽しいね
As expected, games are so much fun!
WE ARE GAMERS!
こうしてさいたまスーパーアリーナに
And that's how we arrived here...
俺たちが訪れたってわけ
...at Saitama Super Arena!
シャキーン！
Shakin'!
本日もいっぱいでございますな！
It's full today too, isn't it!
ありがたいですね。
We're so grateful.
や、ありがたいですよ本当に。
Yeah, truly grateful, honestly.
ということで、
And so...
さあ！始まりましたホロライブゲーマーズフェス！
Now! Hololive Gamers Fes has begun!
超超超超ゲーマーズ2 Day 2です！
It's Super-Super-Super-Super Gamers 2 Day 2!
ということで皆さん、
And so, everyone...
コンコンきつねー！
Kon kon kitsune!
やーさすがです。どうも、なぜかゲーマーズの掛け声ではヨシヒサさんって白上よ。
As expected! Hello, for some reason I'm called 'Yoshihisa' in Gamers cheers.
白上フブキです！よろしくお願いします。
I'm Shirakami Fubuki! Nice to meet you.
そして続いては！
And next up is...
はい！ウチウチウチだよ！
Yes! Uchi uchi uchi da yo!
大神ミオだよー！
It's Ookami Mio!
大神ミオの皆さん、今日も盛り上げよろしくお願いいたします！
Ookami Mio's fans, let's get hyped today too!
そしてー！
And next!
はい！
Yes!
みんな行くよー！
Everyone, here we go!
もぐもぐおかゆー！
Mogu mogu Okayu!
よくできました。どうも。
Well done. Hello.
ホロライブゲーマーズの猫又おかゆです。
I'm Nekomata Okayu from Hololive Gamers.
今日もよろしくお願いします。あの、出禁にならないようにね…頑張ります。
Treat me well today too. Um, I'll try my best not to get banned.
そして！
And!
はい！みんな行くよー！
Yes! Everyone, here we go!
ジャン・ケン・ポン！
Rock-Paper-Scissors!
ジャンケンじゃねえよ！
It's not rock-paper-scissors!
戌神ころねです！よろしくお願いします。
I'm Inugami Korone! Please treat me well.
大谷翔平の次、ジャンケン…
After Shohei Ohtani, comes rock-paper-scissors...
もうころねすきー、それでも全然平気だった？今大丈夫だった？
Koronesukis, were you really okay with that? Are you alright?
てことで改めまして、ホロライブゲーマーズフェス超超超超ゲーマーズ2 Day 2が、
So once again, Hololive Gamers Fes Super-Super-Super-Super Gamers 2 Day 2,
ここさいたまスーパーアリーナで開幕じゃー！
is starting right here at Saitama Super Arena!
やーなんと、Day 1、Day 2合わせると、なんと3万5約3万5千人以上が！
Wow, combining Day 1 and Day 2, apparently over 35,000, about 35,000 people!
てことで、今日のDay 2はなんと、1万7千人ぐらいいるらしいですよ！
And so, for today's Day 2, apparently there are about 17,000 people here!
すごい！
Amazing!
すごい！上のほうも皆いますよ、ほら！
Amazing! Everyone's even in the top rows, look!
見えてる？そこ見えてる？
Can you see? Can you see from there?
大丈夫？
You okay?
左右も見えてますかー？見えてるかなー？
Can the left and right sides see too? Can you see?
去年はですね、あのミオが来れなかった、
Last year, you see, Mio couldn't make it,
国立代々木競技場第一体育館だったんですけども、
to the National Yoyogi Stadium First Gymnasium, but...
さらに今回は大きな、大きな大きな場所でやらせていただくことになりました！
this time, we get to perform in an even bigger, bigger, bigger venue!
4人でやらせていただけて本当にありがとうございます！全員で立つことができました。
Thank you so much for letting us do this as four! We're all standing here together.
さて改めてこのイベントではですね、ゲームが大好きを我々を中心に、
Now then, in this event, centered around us who love games,
超超超超豪華なゲストの皆様と一緒に、
together with super-super-super-super gorgeous guests,
様々なゲームタイトルに挑戦したり、ライブパフォーマンスをお届けするプレミアムイベントとなってます！
we'll challenge various games and deliver live performances in this premium event!
しかも今回ですね、もう皆さんお分かりかと思いますが、Day 1に続き4人の、
And this time, as I'm sure you've noticed, following Day 1, the four of us have...
お揃いTシャツ！
Matching T-shirts!
さらにさらに会場ではですね、一部撮影OKなパートがありますので、
Furthermore, in the venue, there are parts where filming is partially allowed,
そちらもお楽しみに！ぜひ最後まで皆さん、
so look forward to that too! Everyone, until the very end...
盛り上がっていけますかー！？
Can we get hyped!?
てことでね、我々ゲーマーズからも一人ずつ意気込みを言っていきたいと思いますよ。
And so, we Gamers would each like to express our enthusiasm.
最終日、まずはミオしゃから！
On this final day, starting with Mio-sha!
はい！
Yes!
えーとですね、昨日の意気込みで、あの明日も…
Um, well, in yesterday's enthusiasm, about tomorrow...
体調を崩さないように頑張るっていう風にね
I said I'd do my best not to get sick...
お話しさせていただいたんですけど
...as I mentioned before.
もう今日はこの会場にね、いてこのステージに立ってるっていうことは
But since I'm already at this venue and on this stage,
どんなに体調崩そうとも帰れないっていうことなので
it means I can't go home no matter how sick I get!
やめて体調崩さないで！
Stop it, don't get sick!
頑張るから！
I'll do my best!
あ、無理はしないよ
Ah, I won't overdo it.
最後まで笑顔で走り切る、頑張りたいと思います
I'll run through to the end with a smile!
みんな一緒に盛り上がっていこう！
Let's all get excited together!
続きまして、おかゆん！
Next up, Okayun!
はい！
Yes!
まあ、昨日はね
Well, yesterday...
逆打率3割を目標に、大谷翔平ね、頑張ったんですけど
I worked hard aiming for a 30% reverse batting average, like Shohei Ohtani.
ちょっと逆に頑張りすぎて、微妙に出禁になりかけたので
But I worked a bit too hard and almost got banned from the venue.
今日は、まあ、ほどほどに
So today, well, moderately...
逆にほどほどに、楽しんでいきたいと思います
I want to enjoy it 'moderately' instead.
ほどほどは何割ぐらいなんですか？
How many percent is 'moderately'?
2.5
昨日の上じゃん！
That's even higher than yesterday!
昨日なんかドッキリの内容を受けたんですけど
I received some feedback on yesterday's pranks...
政治部とかさ
...like the 'Political Club' thing.
何だっけ？
What was that?
政治部やらされたり
Being made to do the 'Political Club'...
ボケてますよ、この猫
This cat is playing dumb!
本当に、どんなんでしたっけ？
Seriously, what was it like?
どんなんでしたっけ？
What was it like?
嫌です！やりません！
I hate it! I won't do it!
さいたまスーパーアリーナで歌わされたり
Being made to sing at Saitama Super Arena...
すずめとかさ
...like 'Suzume' and all.
可愛かったよね
It was cute, wasn't it?
おかしいんだよな、満足度は高かったです
It's strange, but the satisfaction was high.
大谷さんの話をしていた
The one who was talking about Ohtani-san...
はい！
Yes!
ころねです！
It's Korone!
昨日はね、ちょっと翔平のためにとか言って
Yesterday, I said it was for Shohei...
一部のころねすきがね、ぴきぴきピーマンになってたので
...and some Koronesuki got all grumpy.
今日はころねすきのために頑張ります！
So today, I'll work hard for the Koronesuki!
可愛い！喜んでるよ、みんな
Cute! Everyone is so happy!
あと翔平ごめん！
Also, sorry Shohei!
はい、そして白上もですね
Yes, and for Shirakami too...
今日もですね、たくさん読み上げることが多いと思うんですけども
I think there will be a lot of announcements today as well.
その間、あの、この3人がきっと
Meanwhile, I'm sure these three...
いっぱい面白おかしいことやってくれるんじゃないかと思っておりますので
...will do many funny and strange things.
白上のお話にも耳を貸しつつ
So please listen to Shirakami's talk,
おめめはですね、あの上の大きいモニターと
but keep your eyes on the big monitor above,
そしてあの可愛い3人を見ていただいて
and look at these three cute members.
最後皆さんでね、笑って帰れるといいなと思ってます
I hope we can all go home laughing at the end.
さあ、そして昨日と今日行われる「超超超超ゲーマーズ2」は
Now, for 'Cho-Cho-Cho-Cho Gamers 2' held yesterday and today,
ABEMA PPVで生配信してます！
it's being live-streamed on ABEMA PPV!
コメントのみんな、見てるー？
Everyone in the comments, are you watching?
見てるよー！草生えてるー！
I see you! LOLs are everywhere!
大谷はゴリラってコメントもね
There's a comment saying 'Ohtani is a gorilla'!
やめろ！
Stop it!
配信チケットは絶賛発売中です！
Streaming tickets are now on sale!
イベントが終わっても、8月4日の23時59分まで見ることができます！
You can watch it until August 4th, 23:59!
購入特典として、Day1とDay2で異なるシチュエーションの限定オリジナルボイスドラマがついてきます！
As a purchase bonus, you get limited original voice dramas!
Day1は、秘密の事前プロデュースボイス
Day 1: 'Secret Pre-Produce Voice'
秘密？秘密？
Secret? Secret?
そしてDay2は、内緒のお疲れ様ボイスとなっております
And Day 2 is 'Secret Post-Event Voice'.
内緒ってどの程度内緒なんですか？
How much of a secret is it?
内緒だよ！
It's a secret!
あとはですね、我々からの直筆メッセージ入りのライブ画像、ライブリ…ライブリって何だ
Also, you get a live photo with a handwritten message...
直筆メッセージ入りのライブ画像もついてきますので
...a live photo with a handwritten message is included.
ぜひチェックしてみてください！
Please check it out!
さらに昨年行われました「超超超超ゲーマーズ」のダイジェストがABEMAプレミアムで公開中！
Last year's digest is now on ABEMA Premium!
昨年のね、楽しかった場にミオはいらっしゃらないんですけども
Mio wasn't there for last year's event,
4人でも頑張らせていただきましたので、その様子いっぱい見てください！
but the four of us worked hard, so please watch it!
さらにさらに！イベント後にグッズの受注販売が開始中！
Also, post-event merchandise pre-orders have started!
こちらの期間は、7月21日の23時59分まで！
The period is until July 21st, 23:59!
Cyber Goods Storeにて受付中で、10月中旬頃からお届けです
Available at Cyber Goods Store, delivery in mid-October.
こちらも予約したよっていう人いますか？
Has anyone pre-ordered yet?
いるいる！
We did! We did!
みんな予約してるって言ってる！
Everyone says they pre-ordered!
事後通販ありがとうございます！
Thank you for the post-event sales!
当日販売のグッズはすべて売り切れと聞いております！皆さんありがとうございました！
I heard venue merch is all sold out! Thank you everyone!
ランダムで推しゲットできたかい？
Did you get your favorite in the random items?
できた？できた？よかった！ありがとうございます！
You did? Good! Thank you so much!
会場でゲットできなかったよーという方がいらっしゃいましたらね
If there's anyone who couldn't get it at the venue,
是非とも事後通販で受注販売しておりますのでゲットしてください！
please get it through the post-event mail-order! They're made-to-order!
そしてさらにさらにさらに！もうご存知の方もいらっしゃると思いますが...
And further, further, further! As some of you may already know...
NTTドコモさんのhome 5Gとコラボキャンペーン実施中でーす！
A collaboration campaign with NTT Docomo's home 5G is underway!
あ、しましただね、これ、実施し終わっちゃったんだ
Oh, it says 'conducted'... so it already ended.
えー、デカタオルや入口でもらえるうちわ
Um, the big towel and the fan you get at the entrance,
皆さんゲットしましたかー？
did everyone get them?
ちゃんとやりましたよーって人！
For those who got them, let me see!
お、いらっしゃいます、ありがとうございます！
Oh, I see some! Thank you!
水分補給とか万全にして
Make sure to stay hydrated
最後までお楽しみくださーい！ありがとうございます！
and enjoy until the end! Thank you!
あ、すみません！こちらですね、事後限定グッズとしまして
Ah, excuse me! About this, as post-event limited goods,
アクリルパネルがそういえば追加されてるんですよ、皆さん知ってましたー？
acrylic panels have been added! Did you all know?
そう、実はアクリルパネル、こちらね、あの事後限定グッズなので...
Yes, actually, these acrylic panels are post-event limited goods...
今「あ、そういえば」って思った方は是非ともゲットしてください！
So if you just thought, "Oh, that's right!", please get them!
あの、あの、やめて！うわーっ！ごめんなさーい！
Um, um, stop! Whoa! I'm sorry!
まだまだ続きまーすからね！
There's still much more to come!
えー、我々ゲーマーズを応援したいという声が多かったので
Since many people wanted to support Gamers,
今回のイベントでCheerSPOTさんとのコラボ、決定ー！
we've decided to collab with CheerSPOT for this event!
イェーイ！
Yay!
誰でも簡単に好きなCheerSPOTの場所に
Anyone can easily put up our support ads
我々の応援広告を出すことができます！
at any CheerSPOT location they like!
是非ともね、これ白上も割と日頃利用させていただいておりますので、嬉しいですね
Please do! Shirakami also uses this quite often, so I'm happy.
この会場内でもですね、設置してあるのを見たと思うんですけども
I think you've seen them set up in this venue too,
あんな感じでですね、凄く綺麗に広告出せますので
you can put up ads beautifully like that,
よければよろしくお願いいたします！
so please check it out!
えーさらに、さいたまスーパーアリーナ会場内で、等身大を初披露させていただきました！
Furthermore, we debuted the life-sized figures here at Saitama Super Arena!
3月のEXPO会場で発表された、フブミオ等身大に続きまして...
Following the life-sized Fubu-Mio announced at the March EXPO...
おかころのフィギュアも発表されましたー！見てくれましたかー？
Oka-Koro figures were also announced! Did you see them?
また、昨日から新作フィギュアはグッスマさんから
Also, pre-orders for the new figures started yesterday
受注開始ということで、皆さん、予約したかー？
at Good Smile! Did everyone pre-order?
したー！
I did!
めっちゃ可愛かった！めっちゃ可愛かった！
They were so cute! So cute!
超可愛かった、本当。ガチ可愛かった。
They were super cute, seriously. For real.
イベントの開催を記念しまして、8月7日までに
To celebrate the event, those who pre-order
グッスマで予約してくれた方には、特典のステッカープレゼントだそうです！
at Good Smile by August 7th will receive a bonus sticker!
欲しい！欲しい！
I want it! I want it!
おかころも出たんですけど、フブミオが終わっちゃったーと思ってたんですが
Oka-Koro are out, and I thought Fubu-Mio was over, but...
なんと！期間限定でフブミオの追加予約も開始してまーす！
Guess what! Additional pre-orders for Fubu-Mio have also started!
最高！最高！
The best! The best!
是非ともゲーマーズ4人揃えれる方は揃えてみろ！
If you can collect all four Gamers, go for it!
揃えれる方は揃えてみてね！お願いします！
Please try to collect them all! Thank you!
そして最後に、カンダフル様による協賛企業グッズ
And finally, the sponsored goods by Kandaful,
「超×4 ポップコーン」と「超×4 グリルチキン」です！
"Cho x4 Popcorn" and "Cho x4 Grilled Chicken"!
素敵ー！素敵ー！
Lovely! Lovely!
今回のイベントのキービジュアルが全面に出たデザインとなっているとのことでして
The design prominently features the event's key visual.
ポップコーンは税込1000円、缶詰は税込1500円で販売でーす！
Popcorn is 1000 yen, and the canned chicken is 1500 yen!
ポップコーンは塩キャラメル味、缶詰はグリルチキンになってます！
The popcorn is salt caramel, and the can is grilled chicken!
イェーイイェーイイェーイ！
Yay yay yay!
これ、ポップコーンの方にはランダムトレカがついてるそうなので、よろしくお願いします！
The popcorn comes with a random trading card, so check it out!
食べてる食べてる。美味しい！美味しい！
They're eating it. It's delicious! Delicious!
なんと！サイバーグッズストアでは
Guess what! At the Cyber Goods Store,
こちらのポップコーンと缶詰が完売になってしまったー！
the popcorn and canned chicken are sold out!
えーっ！！ なんですけど...
What?!! But...
なんと本日22時から追加販売が決定しましたー！
additional sales will start from 10 PM tonight!
イェーイ！
Yay!
こちらのグッズはですね、他のグッズと異なりまして
Unlike other goods, please note that these
受注販売ではなく数量限定商品のためご注意ください！
are limited quantity items, not made-to-order!
サイバーグッズストアの他に、カンダフルの公式通販サイトでも
Besides the Cyber Goods Store, they're also sold
販売してますので、皆さんチェックお願いします！
on Kandaful's official site, so please check it out!
集合アクリルパネルも含めてですね、事後でしか購入できないグッズなので
Including the group acrylic panel, these are goods you
皆さん是非確認してください！
can only buy after the event, so please check!
なんかデジャヴなんですけど
I feel like I've seen this before...
混ざっておいで、ゲーマーズ列車にほら。あ、終点、終点、終点。
Join in the Gamers train! Ah, terminal, terminal, terminal.
ブブミオ駅、ブブミオ駅。乗らなきゃ、終点終点。
Bubumio Station, Bubumio Station. Must board, terminal, terminal.
いってらっしゃーい！
Have a safe trip!
間もなく発車、終点終点。え、終わっちゃった。
Departing soon, terminal, terminal. Oh, it ended.
え、また昨日に引き続きまして、本日も韓国のライブビューイング開催されてまーす！
Also, continuing from yesterday, the live viewing in Korea is being held today too!
韓国の皆さん、見てますかー？
Everyone in Korea, are you watching?
アンニョンハセヨー！ 韓国の皆さんヤッホーー！ カムサハムニダー！
Annyeonghaseyo! Everyone in Korea, yoo-hoo! Kamsahamnida!
韓国の方もですね、終わった後とか始まる前とかに
The fans in Korea also took many group photos
やっぱ集合写真いっぱい撮ってくださってて、投稿確認させていただきました！
before and after the show, I saw your posts!
今日もよろしくお願いしまーす！ サランヘー！
Please enjoy today too! Saranghae!
サランヘヨー！
Saranghaeyo!
さぁ、では早速ですね、最初に行うゲームタイトル発表していきましょうかね！
Now, without further ado, let's announce the first game title!
はい！ はい！ はい！
Yes! Yes! Yes!
（笑い声）
(Laughing)
はい、じゃあ行きますよ！
Alright, here we go!
はい！
Yes!
せーの！
Ready, set...
ドン！
Bang!
ギャングビースト！
Gang Beasts!
はい、こちらゼリーのようにぷにゃぷにゃとキャラクターたちが
Here, these characters are squishy like jelly...
危険なステージで
...on dangerous stages,
どたばたバトル乱闘を繰り広げる
unfolding a slapstick chaotic battle...
ちょっとおバカなマルチプレイヤーパーティーゲームです。
...a slightly silly multiplayer party game.
今回は、2対2のチーム戦と個人戦の2マッチで対決したいと思います！
This time, we'll compete in two matches: a 2v2 team battle and an individual battle!
イエーイ！
Yeay!
こちら勝利すると、頭の後ろにですね、星のバルーンがつきます。
When you win, a star balloon will be attached to the back of your head.
最終的にバルーンが一番多い人が勝利となります。
In the end, the person with the most balloons wins.
ということで、早速やっていきますよー！
So, let's get started right away!
ウホホホホ！
Uhohoho!
じゃあ最初のマッチは2対2のチーム戦ということで
Well, for the first match, it's a 2v2 team battle...
チームはそうですね、先ほどあみだで決めました。
...the teams were decided by Amida lottery earlier.
フブおかチームと、みおころチーム！
Fubu-Oka team and Mio-Koro team!
ということで、こちら...
So, over here...
にゃばいです！
We're Nya-bye!
二人合わせて、にゃばいですね！ドン！
Together, we're Nya-bye-desu! Bang!
合ってるかな？合ってる？合ってる？
Is it right? Is it? Is it?
合ってる、合ってる。
It's right, it's right.
たぶんギリギリ合ってる。
Probably barely right.
ギリギリ！
Barely!
ということでこちらでね、対決して行きたいと思います。
So, we'll be competing with this.
ちょっと待って！なんか無いですか？
Wait a minute! Isn't there something else?
え、何がですか？
Eh, what is it?
え、なんかこう掛け声とか、チーム名とか。
Like, a call or a team name.
ありますよ！
We have one!
え、じゃあ教えてください！
Eh, then please tell me!
まずは...
First...
お姉ちゃんのおかゆさーん！
Big sister Okayu~!
妹のフブちゃんです！
I'm the little sister, Fubu-chan!
二人合わせて...
Together we are...
二人合わせて、ヤングコーンずです！
Together we are, Young Corns!
え、すっと言っていいですか？
Eh, can I say something?
ダメです！
No!
ダメなんかい！
You're saying no?!
なんか弱み握られてない？
Aren't you being blackmailed?
なんかちょっといじられてたかもしれない。
Maybe she was being teased a bit.
とりあえずこの空気に流されている。
For now, I'm just going with the flow.
準備できたからほら、後ろにコントローラーがあるから。
Preparation is done, so look, there are controllers in the back.
せやらしい。
Apparently so.
自分のカラー取ってね、ちゃんと。
Take your own color, okay?
はい、ということで、コントローラーでやっていきたいと思います。
So, we'll be playing with the controllers.
ではゲーム画面切り替えてもらってください！
Now, please switch to the game screen!
なんか両手上げてますけど。
They're raising both hands.
これ誰が誰か、さあみんなわかんないのかな？
Does everyone know who is who?
じゃあさっそく紹介しよう！
Let's introduce the characters!
まずですね、これ青くてなんか白衣着てるのが
First, this blue one in a lab coat...
どうやら白上さんだそうです。
...is apparently Shirakami-san.
どうもどうも。
Hello, hello.
そして、そのお隣が、
And next to her,
がんじがらめの猫の被り物を被ってるのが僕です。
the one wearing a tied-up cat headgear is me.
はい、おかゆ！
Yes, Okayu!
えーと、なんか真っ赤っか、ねこみみっぽいのがうちです。
The bright red one with cat ears is me.
大神ミオです。
I'm Ookami Mio.
「ぎゃはー！」みたいなやつがころね！
The one going "Gyahha!" is Korone!
ということで、まずはね、赤と青に分かれましたチーム戦でございます。
So, first is the team battle divided into Red and Blue.
準備いいですか？
Are you ready?
それでは、ギャングビースト1回戦、スタート！
Now, Gang Beasts 1st match, start!
やるぞコラ！
Let's do this!
頑張ろうおかゆちゃん！
Let's do our best, Okayu-chan!
今から力を見せてやろう！
I'll show you my power now!
行けるよ！ミオしゃ！うちには任せろ！
I can! Mio-sha, leave it to me!
皆様！赤で応援してください！
Everyone! Please cheer for Red!
おらー！
Take that!
あかん、あかん、あかん、コラ！
No, no, no, hey!
やめてー！ぎゃー！
Stop it! Gya!
おらー！何だコラ！
Hey! What's this, hey!
やばい、やばい、やばい！
Dangerous, dangerous, dangerous!
やめろ！
Stop it!
何これ！やばい、やばい、やばい！
What is this! It's bad, bad, bad!
赤、赤、赤！やめろー！
Red, Red, Red! Stop it!
やめろー！やばい！
Stop it! This is bad!
あにゃー！やばいやばい！
Anya! Bad bad!
ぎゃー！やばい！
Gya! This is bad!
頑張れミオしゃ！
Go Mio-sha!
おいお前！おらー！
Hey you! Take that!
ぷにゃぷにゃしてる！
It's so squishy!
待って、ミオしゃ！どこ？手伝って！
Wait, Mio-sha! Where are you? Help me!
もう一人いないから！ぎゃー！
Because no one else is left! Gya!
何休んでるの！
What are you resting for!
待って、もう死んじゃった！待って！
Wait, I'm already dead! Wait!
やめて、やめて、やめて！助けてー！ぎゃー！
Stop it, stop it, stop it! Help! Gya!
（レッドの勝利）
(Red's Victory)
やったー！
We did it!
ミオしゃ、ごめん！ギリギリ刺さった！
Mio-sha, sorry! That was close!
今度はやったぞー！
We did it this time!
ではこれ、二本先取なので、
Now, this is best of three,
二回勝ったチームが勝利ですからね！
so the team that wins twice is the winner!
なんかくっついた！星だ！星だ！
Something stuck! It's a star! It's a star!
We are GAMERS!!!!
もう始まってる！始まってる！
It's already started! It's started!
待って！待って！待って！
Wait! Wait! Wait!
行けー！ほら！どけ！どけ！
Go! Look! Move! Move!
ブルーの勝利
Blue Victory
ヤバイヤバイヤバイ！
Oh no, oh no, oh no!
数の暴力、やばいよね
The numbers game is crazy, right?
ブルーの勝利
Blue Victory
と、いうことで
And so...
負けたー！
We lost!
負けたー。星の数は？
We lost. How many stars?
え？負けた？負けた？負けた？
Eh? We lost? Lost? Lost?
星の数は、
The number of stars is...
1、2、3... 4！
1, 2, 3... 4!
二人合わせて、4！
Combined, that's four!
こっち 102個！
We have 102 here!
数え方変！102個っておかしいでしょ！
That's a weird way to count! 102 is crazy!
ということで、今回はミオ・ころコンビの勝利！
And so, the Mio-Koro duo wins this time!
イェーイ！やったー！
Yay! We did it!
そしてですね、ここで、お知らせでございます。
And now, we have an announcement.
あ、かな？バイバイ！
Oh, is it time? Bye-bye!
無料配信をご覧の皆様はここまでとなります。
This is the end for those watching the free broadcast.
続きを見たい方はぜひ、ABEMA PPVにて購入をお願い致します。
If you'd like to see the rest, please purchase on ABEMA PPV.
よろしくお願いします！
We look forward to it!
バイバイ！
Bye-bye!
痛いよねー
It's painful, isn't it?
はい、この後、個人戦が待ってますからね。
Yes, a solo battle is coming up next.
バチバチにやっていきたいと思いますよ。
We're going to go at it hard.
それでは、またねー！
Well then, see you later!
またねー！バイバイ！
See you! Bye-bye!
無料パートは終了いたしました。全編はABEMA PPVにて視聴可能！
The free part has ended. Full version available on ABEMA PPV!
おかゆ！
Okayu!
ころね！
Korone!
ミオ！
Mio!
おかゆ！
Okayu!
ミオ！
Mio!
ころね！
Korone!
G
A
M
E
R
S